<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MyApplication</string>
    <string name="news_title_1">Kylian Mbappe: Paris St-Germain forward says he has not made up mind on future</string>
    <string name="news_text_1">Paris St-Germain forward Kylian Mbappe says he has not made a decision about his future.
The 25-year-old France captains deal with the Ligue 1 champions runs out in the summer and he has been heavily linked with a move to Real Madrid.
Mbappe told PSG in June that he would not be taking up an option for a further 12 months in his contract.
"First of all, I'm very, very, very motivated for this year. It's very important," said Mbappe.
</string>
    <string name="news_title_2">Jadon Sancho: Manchester United winger might rejoin Borussia Dortmund on loan</string>
    <string name="news_text_2">Manchester United outcast Jadon Sancho might return to Borussia Dortmund on loan this month.
Sancho refused to apologise to Erik ten Hag for a social media post after the manager said his omission from Septembers defeat at Arsenal was related to his performance in training.
The England winger, 23, rejected this and said he was being made a scapegoat.
Since then he has been training away from the first team, with no end in sight to his exile.
</string>
    <string name="news_title_3">Tottenham sign Australia defender from Swedish side Vittsjo</string>
    <string name="news_text_3">Tottenham have signed Australia defender Charlotte Grant from Swedens Vittsjo GIK on a contract until 2026.
The 22-year-old full-back has 21 international caps and was in the Australia squad beaten by England in last summers World Cup semi-final.
She is Tottenhams second signing of 2024, following the arrival of Sweden attacking midfielder Matilda Vinberg.
    </string>
    <string name="news_title_4">Ronaldo ended the Year as the Top Scorer with a total of 54 Goals</string>
    <string name="news_text_4">Once the best soccer player in the world, Portuguese Cristiano Ronaldo, despite turning 39 soon, ended the year as the top scorer with a total of 54 goals.
The striker of Al-Nassr scored the last goal in the triumph against Al Tavun (4:1) on Saturday night.
Kylian Mbappe (PSG) and Harry Kane (Bayern) were behind him with 52 goals each.
Many fans previously suggested that Ronaldo should consider retirement following his exit from Old Trafford in November 2022.</string>



</resources>